Lloyd Wright papers LSC.1561
UCLA Library Special Collections
Lloyd Wright papers
1920-1978
UCLA Library Special Collections
Wright, Lloyd, 1890-1978
LSC.1561
83 linear feet (42 boxes, 62 cartons, and 375 oversize folders)
Lloyd Wright (1890-1978) was the eldest son of Frank Lloyd Wright. He trained as a draftsman/delineator in his father's Oak Park Studio, and studied engineering at the University of Wisconsin (1908-09). He was a landscape architect for various Los Angeles projects (1922-24), provided the shells for the Hollywood Bowl (1924-25 and 1928), and produced the Swedenborg Memorial Chapel (or Wayfarer's Chapel) at Palos Verdes, California (1946-71). The collection consists of Wright's original drawings, renderings, blueprints, photographs, models and office files. Many of the photographs in the collection are by Will Connell.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Eric Lloyd Wright, purchase, 1990.
Gift of Eric Lloyd Wright, 1993.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9936492913606533
Biography
Lloyd Wright, eldest son of Frank Lloyd Wright, was born in 1890; trained as a draftsman/delineator in his father's Oak Park Studio; studied engineering, University of Wisconsin, 1908-09; joined Olmsted and Olmsted in Boston, Massachusetts; sent to San Diego, California, to work on Panama California Exposition, 1911; worked for Irving J. Gill; formed landscape architectural practice with Paul Thiene and continued professional activities as landscape architect through the 1920s; worked with father, Frank Lloyd Wright, on Hollyhock House and other Los Angeles projects, 1922-24; produced project for multilayered civic center, Los Angeles, 1925; provided the shells for the Hollywood Bowl, 1924-25 and 1928; much of his work from 1930s through post-World War II dealt with variations of California ranch houses; produced Swedenborg Memorial Chapel (or Wayfarer's Chapel) at Palos Verdes, California, 1946-71; died in 1978.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of original drawings, renderings, blueprints, photographs, models and office files of Southern California architect Lloyd Wright. Includes materials related to over 360 of Wright's architectural projects. Also includes correspondence between Wright and his father, Frank Lloyd Wright, about the Hollyhock House, Los Angeles, California. Many of the photographs in the collection are by Will Connell.
Organization and Arrangement
This collection has been arranged in the following series: in the following series:
Series 1: Files
Series 2: Blueprints, plans, drawings, photos, renderings, and other material
Hollywood Bowl (Los Angeles, Calif.) -- Designs and plans; Architectural drawings (visual works).; Photographs.; Notebooks.; Blueprints.; Architecture -- California, Southern -- 20th century.; Architects -- California -- Los Angeles -- Archives; Hollyhock House (Hollywood, Los Angeles, Calif.); Wayfarers' Chapel--Designs and plans.; Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1867-1959--Correspondence.; Wright, Lloyd, 1890-1978--Archives.
- Series 1: Files
  - Inventions
    - Foiltex - Copper roof, Project No.: [no number assigned]
      - Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 17)
      - Roof & wash surface patent letters, 1937 (Box 92, Folder 18)
      - Roof & wash surface patent letters, 1941 (Box 92, Folder 19)
      - Brochures, drawings & patents (Box 92, Folder 20)
      - Photos by Mott Studios (1 of 2) (Box 92, Folder 21)
      - Photos by Mott Studios (2 of 2) (Box 92, Folder 22)
      - La Voie (Box 92, Folder 23)
      - Building units & stock requirements (Box 92, Folder 24)
      - Commissioners data (Box 92, Folder 25)
      - Celo-Tex (1 of 2) (Box 92, Folder 26)
      - Celo-Tex (2 of 2) (Box 92, Folder 27)
      - Various patents (Box 92, Folder 28)
      - Canadian patents (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Original patent (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Swanfeldt copper roofs (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Bills & receipts (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Report on copper roofing (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Patents (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Strap wrap (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Griffith roof (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Agreements (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Blueprints (Box 93, Folder 10)
      - LA County DA investigation (Box 93, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence (Box 93, Folder 12)
      - Insolite Co. - correspondence (Box 93, Folder 13)
      - Core studies (Box 93, Folder 14)
      - General (Box 93, Folder 15)
      - Copper Roof Corp. & New Haven Roof Co. (Box 93, Folder 16)
      - Technical - Foiltex data (Box 93, Folder 17)
      - Anaconda Copper - correspondence (Box 93, Folder 18)
      - Technical - Dennis La Voie Corp. correspondence (Box 93, Folder 19)
      - Technical - Griffith roof data (Box 93, Folder 20)
      - Technical - cost data (Box 93, Folder 21)
      - Advertising (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence & notes (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Justice, Jack - Global simulator, Project No.: 359
      - General (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Justice, Jack - Speaker resonator
      - Patent details (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Bills (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - Patent applications (Box 92, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence (Box 92, Folder 14)
      - Construction detail & cost, and negatives (Box 92, Folder 15)
      - Walton agreement (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Wright, Lloyd - Color film, Project No.: [no number assigned]
      - General (1 of 2) (Box 93, Folder 23)
      - General (2 of 2) (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Office Files
    - Financial Records - Bank statements and loan papers
      - 1960s - 1970s (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Financial Records - Bank statements
      - 1960s - 1970s (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - 1930s - 1970s (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Financial Records - Checkbooks
      - 1975 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Lloyd Wright - Memorial Service
      - Condolences to family from city of Los Angeles, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Announcements (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Programs (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Condolences file (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Lloyd Wright - Address books
      - (2 folders) (Box 101, Folder 10, Folder 11)
    - Lloyd Wright - Calendar, [insect damaged]
      - 1937 (Box 95, Folder 17)
      - 1938 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - 1939 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - 1940 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - 1941 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - 1943 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - 1944 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - 1945 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - 1946 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - 1947 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - 1948 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - 1949 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - 1950 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - 1951 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - 1951 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - 1952 (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - 1953 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - 1954 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - 1955 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - 1956 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - 1957 (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - 1958 (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - 1960 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - 1961 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - 1962 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - 1963 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - 1971 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Lloyd Wright - Correspondence
      - Taggart, Martha (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
      - Hillside Home & School - Wisconsin (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Oasis Hotel - Mary Kellogg Sherrill (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Tibbett, Lawrence (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Tibbett, Jane Marston (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Personal finance (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Newman, Alfred (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Foster, Stanton (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Wood, Beatrice (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Cardenas, Francisco (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Gilbert, Mrs. Paul T. (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Jensen, Jens (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Lloyd Wright - Notebook / datebook
      - June 1934 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Lloyd Wright - Notebooks, [insect damaged]
      - 1930 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      - 1935 (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - 1936 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      - 1947 & no date (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - 1947 - 1948 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - 1949 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - 1950 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - 1951 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - 1952 (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - 1953 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - 1954 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - 1955 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - 1956 (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - 1957 (Box 99, Folder 10)
      - 1958 (Box 99, Folder 12)
      - no date (Box 101, Folder 12)
      - 1959 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - 1960 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - 1961 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Lloyd Wright - Office
      - Doheny property, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Doheny studio - bids & contracts unaccepted (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Doheny studio receipts (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Doheny studio - labor & materials (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Doheny studio - receipts, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Christmas designs, 1963, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Christmas list, 1948 - 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Business cards (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Job notes, office records, 1944 - 1952 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Job notes, office records, 1944 - 1952 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Project lists - various (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Job notes, 1949 - 1950 (1 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Job notes, 1949 - 1950 (2 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Job notes, 1949 - 1950 (3 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Notes, 1956 - 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Reminder lists & yellow notes, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Reminder lists & yellow notes, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Reminder lists & yellow notes, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Reminder lists & yellow notes, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Job notes (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Reminder lists & yellow notes, 1955 - 1956 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Specifications - architects & engineers (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Specifications - gas heating (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Specifications - cold storage for FLW plan (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Specifications - building materials (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Specifications - E.R. Lewis (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Specifications - Mrs. S.M.B. Hunt, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Irving Freese - school district (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Erickson - Holiday stations (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Erickson family memorial, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Architects - school employment (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Airways Engineering (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - San Dieguito Unitarian Church (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Chernyk, Mollie, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Kurfin notes, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Sjardema, H. - 1945 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Hodel, Dr. - correspondence & agreement, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Hodel - folder B (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Hodel - construction (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Hodel - sub-contractor's construction (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Hodel - bids (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Hodel - invoices, receipts (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Penn, Albert - Lot 7, blk. 3, tract 7256, Bel Air (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Leigh, Ann. G. - preliminary data, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Rainer, Louise - 1944 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Curtis, Thomas J. - 1946 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Newman, Alfred - 1940 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Navy dwelling - 1944 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Schwarger - 1945 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Fairbanks, Douglas - 1937 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Riskin - 1937 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - King Directors' Club - 1938 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Campbell, Allen - proposal, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Considine, John. W., Jr. - additions, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Russell, Sidney - 1933 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Block remodel - 1935 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Lyon & Lyon Co. - patent lawyers (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Gardner, Sam - map, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Brunswig, Lucien - remodel, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Wilkinson - Vendome Inc., 1929? (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Audac (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Schwinger - tea garden, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Schwinger, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Prospective client folder (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Hill 'an Dale Nursery - reconstruction & restoration, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Hill 'an Dale Nursery (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Project lists (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - LW studio #37 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - UCSB exhibit - 1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Inventions (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Unity Temple (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Griffith, Raymond - house (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Architectural publications - correspondence (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Pilgrimage Theatre, 1961 - 1962 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Valley Unitarian - Universalist Church (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - UCSB exhibit - 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - unspecified (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - UCSB exhibit - architect's notes (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - UCSB exhibit - architect's notes (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - UCSB exhibit - job notes, includes photos of models (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - UCSB exhibit - buildings & projects by LW (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - UCSB exhibit materials - photos (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - UCSB exhibit - David Gebhard (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - UCSB exhibit - David Gebhard (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - UCSB exhibit - David Gebhard - correspondence (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - UCSB exhibit - David Gebhard - correspondence (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Japanese publications - gift of Etsuzo Otari (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Japanese screens - photos by David Wright, April - May 1962 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Kyoto (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Nagoya (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Tokyo data folders - Japanese trip (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Japanese file (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Tokyo (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Imperial Hotel sketches by LW - 1962 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Letters of introduction (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Honolulu - Japanese trip (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Lectures, radio, TV - Japanese trip (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Japanese newspapers re LW, FLW - 1962 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Japanese trip newspapers (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Japanese trip newspapers (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Japan trip itinerary (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Japanese addresses (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Tanigawa, Masami - correspondence, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Tanigawa, Masami - correspondence, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Tanigawa, Masami - correspondence, 1965, 1967, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Frank Lloyd Wright by Masami Tanigawa - inscribed copy (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - FLW literature (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Tanigawa, Masami - photos from April 1963 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Hakone - Nara - Osaka (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Moorehead, S.F. (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Moorehead, S.F. (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Moorehead, S.F. - residence additions (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Moorehead, S.F. - estimate of cost (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Moorehead, S.F. - job notes, certificates, plan checks & records (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Office bookkeeping - LW & FLW building lists (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - File listings - typed (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Sample list & index record - 1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - FLW & LW building lists - 1967 & 1970 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Lair, Max - notes & cuts (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Lair, Max - land surveys (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Lair, Max - architect (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Lair, Max - estimates (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Lair, Max - specifications (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Lair, Max - plan checks & records (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Lair, Max - construction (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Lair, Max - periodicals (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Lair, Max - logo & brochure (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Lair, Max - publications & publicity (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Lair, Max - brochures (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Lair, Max - correspondence (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Federal Works Agency - Change order records (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Federal Works Agency - Change order records (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Federal Works Agency - Change order records - electrical (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Federal Works Agency - Federal change orders - plumbing (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Federal Works Agency - Federal change orders - heating & ventilating (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Federal Works Agency - Change order records (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Office accounts - various projects (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Office accounts - various projects (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Office accounts - 1968 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Notes (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Westfair Shopping Center - dental suite (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Valencia Gardens & Vallejo project (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Plan for Benicia project (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Martin - Fann Shopping Center (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Martin - Fann Shopping Center (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence & miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Westfair Shopping Center (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - California Housing & Planning Asso. (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Programs & agendas (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Wires & correspondence (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Wright, David - client file (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Wright, David - architect (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Wright, David - estimates (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Wright, David - specifications (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Wright, David - construction (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Clients accounts (closed) - grouping 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Clients accounts (closed) - grouping 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Clients accounts (closed) - grouping 3 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Clients accounts (closed) - grouping 4 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Bellenson - specifications & drawings (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Bellenson - specifications & drawings (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Crosby residence interior elevations (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Aliso Village - notes & change orders (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Co-op planners - Washington & L.A. (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Contracts (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Housing Group Architects - correspondence, 1939 - 1941. Cal. 4 - 5 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Huntington Beach Shopping Center (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Huntington Beach Shopping Center (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Christmas ard list, 1969 - 1971 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Letterhead paper (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Christmas cards [blank], no date [gold & white] (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Christmas cards [blank], no date [gold / orange / grey] (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Christmas cards [blank], 1968 [gold / plastic] (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Records - Ledgers
      - 1922 - 1937 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - 1950 - 1959 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - 1960 - 1969 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Records - Receipt book
      - LW, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Records - Telephone message pads
      - 1955, 1957, 1959 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Records - Time books
      - 1946 - 1951 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Records - Time cards
      - 1974 (Box 101, Folder 14)
      - (1 of 2), 1951 - 1955 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - (2 of 2), 1951 - 1955 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - 1975 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - 1976 (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - Wright, Eric, 1956 - 1959 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Urban planning - Professional literature
      - Publications and reports re public housing (1 of 2) (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - Publications and reports re public housing (2 of 2) (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - California Housing and Planning Association (1 of 2) (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - California Housing and Planning Association (2 of 2) (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - Council for Planning and Conservation (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - Regional Plan Association of Southern California (1 of 3) (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - Regional Plan Association of Southern California (2 of 3) (Box 94, Folder 14)
      - Regional Plan Association of Southern California (3 of 3) (Box 94, Folder 15)
      - New culture: IBM culture and urban ecology by Lloyd Wright (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Regional planning - early rough notes (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - USC Homecoming Banquet - In honor of Clayton Baldwin
      - 1958 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Utilities - Correspondence
      - Illinois Power Co. (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Project Files
    - Adams, W.M. - Mat house
      - General, Project No. 118 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Alexander, Rev. Robert - Residence
      - Construction - grading plan (Box 86, Folder 16)
      - Notes (Box 86, Folder 17)
      - Client - correspondence (Box 86, Folder 18)
      - Client - notes (Box 86, Folder 19)
      - Construction - job notes (Box 86, Folder 20)
      - Architect / owner agreement (Box 86, Folder 21)
      - Architect - certificates (Box 86, Folder 22)
      - Architect - studies (Box 86, Folder 23)
      - Estimates - cost (Box 86, Folder 24)
      - Estimates - engineering (Box 86, Folder 25)
      - Specifications - general (Box 86, Folder 26)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 86, Folder 27)
      - Supervision journal (Box 86, Folder 28)
    - Antaky, Elias - Residence & landscaping
      - General, Project No. 162 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Avery, Stephen - Residence
      - General, Project No. 102 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence & miscellaneous, Project No. 102 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Remodel bids, Project No. 102 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Specifications, Project No. 102 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Bids, Project No. 102 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Certificates, contracts, & agreements, Project No. 102 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Babcock, Mr. & Mrs. Russell E. - Residence
      - Construction, Project No. 235 (Box 63, Folder 29)
      - Plan checks & records, Project No. 235 (Box 63, Folder 30)
      - Construction - bids, Project No. 235 (Box 63, Folder 31)
      - Construction - supervisor's journal, Project No. 235 (Box 63, Folder 32)
      - Material bills & vouchers, Project No. 235 (Box 63, Folder 33)
      - Engineering & sketch studies, Project No. 235 (Box 63, Folder 34)
      - Elevation studies, Project No. 235 (Box 63, Folder 35)
      - Engineering (Box 63, Folder 36)
      - Structural studies (Box 63, Folder 37)
      - Client correspondence (Box 63, Folder 38)
      - Plan studies - owner's requests (Box 63, Folder 39)
      - Client notes (Box 63, Folder 40)
      - Land survey (Box 63, Folder 41)
      - Architect's agreements & certificates (Box 63, Folder 42)
      - Estimates - quantity survey (Box 63, Folder 43)
      - Estimates - cost (Box 63, Folder 44)
      - Specifications - general (Box 63, Folder 45)
    - Barnsdall Park - Art Center
      - Client - photographs (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Client - notes (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Kenneth Ross (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Client (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Client - Japanese exhibit (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Client - print exhibition (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Personal (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Architect (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Construction - supervision journal (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Plan checks & records (Box 72, Folder 16)
      - Client (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Barnsdall Park - Landscaping
      - Report & schedules - 1921, Project No. no # (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Irrigation system specifications - 1921, Project No. no # (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Planting lists - 1921, Project No. no # (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Drives specifications - 1921, Project No. no # (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Planting - 1921, Project No. no # (Box 53, Folder 14)